Oh, no!
哦   不
Stop staring! You're acting weird again.
别盯着人家   你又举止怪异了
Thank you.
谢谢
Oh, man...
啊   哎
Can't remember the last time I had a beer.
我都不记得上一次喝啤酒是什么时候了
You can't be all that bad, Mister Zombie.
你也坏不到哪儿去嘛   僵尸先生
My...
我的
Name...
名字
You have a name?
你也有名字吗
What is your name?
你叫什么
Rrr...
Rrr
Rrr?
R什么
This stage is not going well.I want to die all over again.
现阶段进展很不顺利  我恨不得再死一遍
Did your name start with R?
你名字的首字母是R吗
Robert?
是罗伯特吗
Richard?
还是理查德
Randy? Uh ...
兰迪   呃
Raphael? Ricardo?
是不是拉斐尔   或者里卡多
Why don't I just call you R?
要不我就叫你R好了
I mean, that's a start, right?
好歹也算个开始   是不是
I want to go home, R.
R   我想回家了
Not safe.
外面不安全
I get that.
这个我明白
And look...
而且   听着
I know that you saved my life and I'm grateful for that.
我知道你救了我的命   我也对此很感激
But you walked me into this place.So I know that you can walk me out again.
但是是你带我走进这个地方的  所以我知道你也能再带着我走出去
Oh, no! She can't leave, she's just got here.
哦不   她不能走   她才刚刚来到这里呢
-Tell her she has to wait, tell her ... they'll notice. -You have...
-快告诉她必须得等   快告诉她   其他僵尸会注意到的  -你必须
to wait.
得等着
They... will...
他们   会
Notice...
注意到你的
Heh, not bad.
哼   说的还不错嘛